swisschalet.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Swiss Chalet

[Home](https://www.swisschalet.com/) /

Welcome to the website of Swiss Chalet Rotisserie and Grill, a division of Cara Operations Limited (“Swiss Chalet”).

Swiss Chalet recognizes your right to privacy and is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of all guests in our restaurants, users of our call-ahead take out and delivery services, as well as visitors to this website and other online forums through which you communicate with us. The intent of this Privacy Policy is to detail our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure by Swiss Chalet of Personal Information you choose to share with us.

## Your Consent

By providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information by Swiss Chalet in accordance with the terms of our Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be effective and binding on you immediately following the posting of such changes to this website. You agree to review our Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy Policy was last modified in April of 2012. Please also see our website’s Terms of Use for other terms and conditions governing your use of our website and our products and services.

## Definitions

“Cookies” means small files sent to your browser from a web server and stored in your computer.

“Information of a Non-Personal Nature” means any non-confidential, non-proprietary information derived from your connection to this website, such as your Internet browser, domain name and referrer link.

“Personal Information” means personally-identifiable information including, without limitation, your name, street address, telephone number, personal e-mail address, credit card information and food preferences.

## Information of a Non-Personal Nature

As a general policy, with the exception of IP addresses, no Personal Information is automatically collected from visitors to the Swiss Chalet website. Swiss Chalet may gather and analyse IP addresses and certain Information of a Non-Personal Nature regarding website usage by visitors to the Swiss Chalet website. Such data is used in an aggregate form to assist Swiss Chalet in determining general usage patterns and to administer, diagnose problems with, and fine tune the layout of the Swiss Chalet website. We may share non-personal, summary, or aggregate customer data with partners and other third parties at our discretion.

## Cookies

Swiss Chalet may use Cookies to store and sometimes track information about your use of our website. In addition to improving the general layout of the website, Cookies allow us to customize our website to each visitor’s individual preferences. Although most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent you from receiving Cookies or to notify you whenever you are sent a Cookie so that you may decide whether or not to accept it. If you decide not to accept a Cookie, you can still enjoy all of the features of our website.

## Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Certain Personal Information may be voluntarily and knowingly provided to us by visitors to Swiss Chalet. When entering a contest or requesting franchise information, for example, we will ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, as well as certain other information.

Swiss Chalet shall collect Personal Information of visitors to Swiss Chalet and shall use all commercially reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information. If you do not want us to have access to your Personal Information, please do not provide it to us. When you do provide your Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use it in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms, including your right to limit our use of the Personal Information (see “Who to Contact” below).

Swiss Chalet may use Personal Information to contact you, to process and store the Personal Information so that we are able to better understand you and how we can improve our products and services, for editorial, feedback or other fully disclosed purposes, such as to enter you into a contest, respond to a future on-line order or respond by e-mail to an inquiry that you posed on-line. We may also match your Personal Information that you provide to us on this website to information contained in our database. Your Personal Information may also be used by Swiss Chalet, or any other division of Cara Operations Limited, to contact you regarding other products or services which may be of interest to you (including those that we may offer jointly with other companies).

We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any of your Personal Information to any third party (with the exception of third parties performing functions on our behalf who have an obligation to keep your information completely confidential or a third party who buys our business) unless you have authorized us to do so.

Swiss Chalet reserves the right to access and/or disclose Personal Information where required to comply with applicable laws or lawful government requests or, in Swiss Chalet’s reasonable opinion, to operate the Swiss Chalet website properly and securely, or to protect Swiss Chalet or visitors to this website. Swiss Chalet, acting reasonably, shall attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual to whom such Personal Information relates prior to disclosure to third parties. Your Personal Information may be stored on servers hosted in the United States or otherwise outside of Canada.

## A Note to Parents

Swiss Chalet is very sensitive to privacy issues and is committed to protecting the on-line privacy of children and making the Internet safe for our users. As a result, no Personal Information should be submitted to or posted on this site by children under the age of 18 without their parent’s or guardian’s permission. In addition, if a user younger than 18 wishes to send us Personal Information, he or she must first give us his or her parent’s or guardian’s e-mail address so that we can obtain their permission, or have the child’s parent or guardian consent on his or her behalf. No Personal Information will knowingly be accepted from a child under 18 before this permission is obtained. Be assured that Swiss Chalet will not condition a child’s participation in any website activity on the child’s disclosure of more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity.

If your child has already provided us with Personal Information, you may ask to see this information for the purpose of correcting it, or ask us to delete this information from our records entirely (see “Who to Contact” below.) 

## Who to Contact

We welcome your feedback. If you have questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, or would like to do any of the following:

  * see Personal Information that you have already sent us so that you can correct,Â update or delete your Personal Information from our files
  * once your child under 18 has sent us Personal Information, see that Personal Information so that you can correct, update or delete it
  * once your child under 18 has sent us Personal Information, delete that Personal Information from our files
  * ask that we not send you mailings or otherwise contact you
  * report any violation of this Privacy Policy

Please contact our Swiss Chalet Privacy Officer by email at [webmaster@cara.com](mailto:webmaster@cara.com) or by regular mail at:

199 Four Valley Drive  
Vaughan, Ontario  
L4K 0B8  
905-760-2244  
Attention: Swiss Chalet Privacy Officer.
